（声音）
[SOUND]
我不是虚无之神，不是世界的切割者。
I am no god of the void, slicer of worlds.
很久以前，当光明侵入我的王国，
Long ago, when light invaded my kingdom,
我的共生孩子背叛了我，把我囚禁在这里。
my symbiote children betrayed me and imprisoned me here.
最后，一个法典被创造出来了。
At last a codex is being created.
这是我获得自由的钥匙。
It is the key to my freedom.
它会打开这个监狱。
It will unlock this prison.
我命令你走遍宇宙的各个角落直到找到这把钥匙。
I order you to search the corners of the universe until you find this key.
给我找抄本。
Find me the codex.
等我逃出去，消灭所有的生命星球，然后
And when I escape and annihilate every living planet and.
摧毁我的共生后代，我就用你们的命来回报你们。
destroy my symbiote offspring, I will reward you with your lives.
所以你是说在这个宇宙里有超级英雄。
So you're saying in this universe there's the superhero people.
嗨，再跟我说说你的紫色外星人朋友他真的很喜欢石头。
Hi, so tell me again about your purple alien friend who really loves stones.
我告诉你吧，外星人不喜欢石头。
I'll tell you what, man, aliens, they do not love stones.
他们没有开始。
They don't start.
不要爱石头。
Do not love stones.
你知道他们喜欢什么吗？
Do you know what they love?
他们喜欢吃大脑，因为那是他们的工作。
They love eating brains because that's what they do.
Señor，他让我的家人消失了五年。
Señor, he made my family disappear for five years.
五年。
Five years.
看，那是一段很长的时间。
See, that is a long time.
好吧。
All right.
我们喝醉了。
We are drunk.
（声音）
[SOUND]
我们回家。
We're home.
我受够了多元宇宙的破事我更喜欢我们的酒保。
I'm so done with the multiverse shit that I like our version of the barman better.
我头疼。
My head hurts.
我觉得我喝醉了，但同时我也宿醉了。
I feel like I'm drunk, but I'm also hungover at the same time.
你想要一个该死的码头？
You want a bloody marina?
我不想喝酒。
I don't want to drink.
怎么，臭牛奶。
Why, gross milk.
你在毁掉这个人的酒吧。
You are destroying this man's bar.
我今天过得很开心。
I'm having a time of my life today.
我宁愿要一杯水。
I'd rather have a glass of water.
像个男人，埃迪。
Be a man, Eddie.
我们应该去当酒保。
We should have been a bartender.
龙舌兰酒！
Tequila!
我做到了。
I did it.
先生吗？
Señor?
那些东西到底是什么？
What the hell were those things?
我生来就有。
I was born with them.
该死的酒吧，我受够了。
Freaking bar, I'm done with this shit.
Kelly Roulet在旧金山报道。
This is Kelly Roulet reporting from San Francisco.
警方仍在努力寻找前记者埃迪·布洛克，并对其进行讯问
Police are still trying to locate former reporter Eddie Brock for questioning after.
帕特里克·穆里根警探的惨死
the tragic death of Detective Patrick Mulligan.
不。
No.
穆里根警探是在佩尔被发现的，那是
Detective Mulligan was found in Pail and that's a.
在这座城市的大教堂里发生了一系列奇怪的事件。
series of bizarre happenings at the city's cathedral.
他们认为是我杀了他。
They think that I killed him.
他能逃避当局多久？
How long can he evade authorities?
只有时间会告诉我们答案。
Only time will tell.
如果我们上了这里的新闻，我们就上了所有地方的新闻。
If we are on the news here, we are on the news everywhere.
我们不能回旧金山，我也不会待在这里
We can't go back to San Francisco and I'm not staying down.
在墨西哥躲一辈子，这是肯定的。
here hiding for the rest of my life in Mexico, that's for sure.
我们要去哪里？
Where will we go?
我不知道。我不知道。
I don't know. I don't know.
这是可行的。
That could work.
这个教堂害我被赶出了纽约。
This church got me kicked out of New York.
真是个混蛋。
What a dick.
我手上还有一堆他的把柄。
I still got a ton of shit on him too.
我一直想去看看自由女神像。
I've always wanted to see the Statue of Liberty.
也许我们可以勒索他。
Maybe we could blackmail him.
还我清白。
Clear my name.
我们走吧。
Let's go.
公路旅行。
Road trip.
我们离开这鬼地方吧。
Let's get the hell out of here.
找零吧。
Take the change.
我们低着头继续前进。
We keep our heads down and we keep moving.
我们正在射杀他。
We are shooting him.
我们在逃亡。
We are on the run.
是的，我们陷入了困境。
Yes, we are in the shit.
是的，但我会吃掉所有妨碍我们的坏人。
Yes, but I will eat every bad guy that gets in our way.
我需要一个标题。
I need a title.
是你干的？
You did that?
是的。
Yes.
有人有麻烦了，我需要燃料上路。
Someone's in trouble and I need fuel for the road.
是的，好的。
Yeah, okay.
这样的。
That way.
蝙蝠侠，艾迪，我们到底是不是致命守护者？
Batman, Eddie, are we the lethal protector or not?
你觉得呢？
Do you think?
这是一个繁忙的。
It's a busy.
耶稣。
Jesus.
可爱。
Cute.
我答应过不吃的。
I promised not to eat it.
他们在斗狗。
They're fighting dogs.
跟狗打架是我的底线，伙计。
I draw the line at fighting dogs, pal.
只有几个。
Just a few.
哦，你，什么？
Oh, yo, what?
你来错地方了。
You're in the wrong place.
哦，你好。
Oh, hello.
这是我们的领土。
This is our territory.
从你们威胁的表情来看，我想我…
Well, I assume by the threatening look on your faces that I, uh…
我应该害怕，对吧？
I ought to be scared, right?
我们应该走错路，蝙蝠侠。
We should take the wrong path, Batman.
我们可以让你离开。
We can let you leave.
我头痛。
I have a headache.
因为我当时喝了很多酒。
On account of the fact that I was drinking a lot.
我要实话实说。
I'm going to be honest.
我有黑暗和不可预测的一面。
I have a really dark and unpredictable side to me.
我们内心都有恶魔。
We all have monsters inside us.
不是这样的。
Not like this.
太黑了，它很可能把你的头扯下来喂你的屁眼。
So dark that it is highly likely to tear your head off and feed it to your asshole.
我在这里。你可以喂我。
I'm here. You can feed it to me.
对，我可以喂他吃。
Yeah, I can feed it to him.
好吧，听着。哇，哇，哇。来吧。
All right, look. Whoa, whoa, whoa. Come on.
我有个建议。
I got a suggestion.
不，别说了。
No, stop speaking.
我不会停止讲话。这是给你的。
I'm not going to stop speaking. This is for you.
我这么做是为了你好，好吗？
I'm doing this for your benefit, all right?
我不需要。
I don't have to.
好吧？只要集中注意力。
Okay? Just pay attention.
我们会发现这些狗都很可爱
We're going to find all of these dogs loving.
永远的家，因为你的所作所为应该受到谴责。
forever homes, because what you're doing is reprehensible.
你妈妈是怎么看你的，伙计？
And what does your mother think of you, man?
我妈妈死了，科莱罗。
My mother's dead, Colero.
你搞得很尴尬。
You made it awkward.
听到这个消息我很难过。
I'm sorry to hear that.
太好了。
Great.
嗯？
Huh?
部分原因。
Part of the matter.
嗯？
Huh?
谢谢你！
Thank you.
我在给你一个机会。
I'm giving you a chance.
亲爱的，我真的，我在给你一个机会。你也许应该接受它。
Sweetie, I'm really, I'm giving you a chance. You should probably take it.
看到了吗？
See?
看到的。
See.
好吧。
Okay.
看到的时候。
See when.
什么时候？
When?
哇。
Whoa.
打电话。
Call the line.
你好，bitch（婊子）。
Hola, bitches.
谁是坏男孩？
Who's a bad boy?
我去买一双结实的鞋。
I'll get some sturdy footwear.
你要去哪里？
You going?
怎么啦？
What?
是吗？
Are you?
我们是来旅游的。
We are.
不。
No.
是的，我们。
Yeah, we.
我们是来旅游的。
We are.
毒液。
Venom.
怎么啦？
What?
我们真的需要在这方面下功夫了。
We're totally going to need to work on that.
来吧。
Come on.
嗯，很好吃。
Mmm, that was delicious.
不客气。
You're welcome.
谢谢你！
Thank you.
你带我去所有最好的地方。
You take me to all the finest places.
我们离开这鬼地方吧。
Let's get the hell out of here.
我的鞋呢？
Where's my shoe?
嘿，伙计。
Oh, hey, buddy.
这是我的鞋。
There's my shoe.
这些合适。
These will fit.
现在我们在为我们确实做过的事奔走。
Now we are on the run for something we actually did do.
我被困在了一个不会飞的超级英雄身上。
And I got stuck with the superhero who can't fly.
一点点。给你。
One a bit. There you are.
给我接思特里克兰德将军。
Get me General Strickland.
什么……
What the…
病毒脱落。
Viral shedding.
这些东西想要生存。
These things want to live.
你好。
Hola.
跟我说说刚才那个人。
Tell me about the man who was just here.
他像疯了一样自言自语。
He was acting like crazy talking to himself.
他在说什么？
What was he saying?
他的手臂又粗又宽。
He had these big, massive, wide arms.
它们像这样冒泡。带他来。（播放音乐）
They were bubbling like this. Bring him. [MUSIC PLAYING]
你觉得他们是另一颗星星上的兄妹吗？
You think they're another brother and sister on one of those stars?
看着同一片天空？
Looking at the same sky?
总有一天我会告诉你的。
I'll be able to tell you one day.
我的双胞胎兄弟。
My twin brother.
未来的NASA科学家。
A future NASA scientist.
一天。
One day.
当雷声轰鸣时，进入室内。
When thunder roars, head indoors.
（播放音乐）
[MUSIC PLAYING]
他靠生命维持系统维持生命。
He's on life support.
马上送他去紧急共生中心
Get him to emergency symbiosis now.
（播放音乐）
[MUSIC PLAYING]
应该是你。
It should be you.
他们刚刚遇到了一个新闻台，这是值得重复的。
They just came across a news desk and it bears repeating.
对于你们所有的外星人爱好者来说，这是悲伤的一天。
For all you alien enthusiasts out there, it's a sad day.
华盛顿终于宣布了51区的退役。
Washington has finally announced the decommissioning of Area 51.
这个有争议的地点因其所谓的外星人试验而闻名。
The controversial site is famous for its alleged testing on aliens.
这是今天的其他新闻。
It's in other news today.
（播放音乐）
[MUSIC PLAYING]
（模糊聊天）
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
这边走。
Right this way.
慢下来。
Slow down.
（播放音乐）
[MUSIC PLAYING]
（模糊聊天）
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
（播放音乐）
[MUSIC PLAYING]
斯特里克兰。
Strickland.
斯特里克兰授权。
Strickland authorized.
[音乐播放]最后发生了什么？
[MUSIC PLAYING] What's finally happening then?
是的，女士。
Yes ma'am.
那里只剩下岩石和尘土。
There'll be nothing left but rock and dust.
和蟑螂。
And roaches.
即使是最大的银行也无法消灭它们。
Even the biggest of banks couldn't kill them.
它们已经存在了大约2.8亿年，而且还在不断增加。
They've been around 280 million years and counting.
我不知道佩恩博士。
I did not know that Dr. Payne.
（播放音乐）
[MUSIC PLAYING]
可以走了。
Good to go.
祝你愉快，格斯。
Have a good one Gus.
你也一样。
You too.
（播放音乐）
[MUSIC PLAYING]
谢谢你！
Thank you.
可以走了。
Good to go.
（模糊聊天）
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
（播放音乐）
[MUSIC PLAYING]
早上好，佩恩医生。
Morning Dr. Payne.
我们会替你保管的。
We'll keep them safe for you.
我还是觉得没人想要我的旧健身馆。
I still don't think anyone wants my old beater gym.
现在你想唤起我的h对情侣吗？
Now would you like to evoke my H-couple?
（播放音乐）
[MUSIC PLAYING]
清晨醒来，思特里克兰德将军。
Early morning wake up General Strickland.
看来你所有的梦想都实现了。
Looks like all your dreams came true.
我知道你一定很不高兴。
I know how that must bug you.
他比你早到一会儿。
He arrived shortly before you did.
我们的新朋友给他们添麻烦了吗？
Did our new friend give them any trouble?
你看，这就是问题所在。
You see that's exactly the problem.
怎么啦？
What?
你的假设是去见朋友。
Your assumption were meeting friends.
早…。
Morning.
连接成功了。
The bonding was successful.
我听到。
I heard.
你脸上总是一副可怕的事情即将发生的表情。
You always have this look on your face like something terrible is imminent.
因为在我的工作中，可怕的事情总是迫在眉睫。
Because in my line of work something terrible is always imminent.
我们控制住了他们。
We contain them.
你研究它们。
You study them.
这就是它的工作原理。
That's how it works.
[音乐播放][模糊的闲聊]
[MUSIC PLAYING] [INDISTINCT CHATTER]
让我们看一看。
Let's have a look.
他的另一个共生体离开他等死。
His other symbiote left him for dead.
我们救了他。
We saved him.
他早就死了。
He would have died.
我会试着降低这些水平。
I'll try lowering those levels.
早上赛迪。
Morning Sadie.
让我回去。
Let me get back.
这是我们在墨西哥拍的。
We got this down in Mexico.
嗨。
Hi.
受欢迎的。
Welcome.
知道其他人在哪里吗？
Any more on where the rest of them is?
你有什么消息我们就告诉我。
We're getting to update me as you have it.
我不明白这种痴迷。
I don't get this obsession.
我告诉过你这支笔是我妈给我做的。
I told you my mom made me this pen.
这是7月。
It's July.
我们在那里见。
I'll see you in there.
这边的每个人都很奇怪。
Everyone on this side is weird.
别烦她，雷克斯。
Leave her alone Rex.
上帝不允许任何人真正享受他们的工作。
God forbid anyone should actually enjoy their work.
（门关闭）
[DOOR CLOSES]
（模糊聊天）
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
51区将在本周末完全关闭。
Area 51 will be fully decommissioned by the end of the week.
反正这只是一场海难，他们厌倦了游客。
It's just a shipwreck anyway and they're tired of the tourists.
我们在这里不存在。
We don't exist down here.
地下100英尺，人类和非人类都无法察觉。
100 feet subsurface, undetectable to any human or non-human.
每个人都从这里给家里打电话。
Everyone's phoning home from here.
我哥哥最大的抱负就是在51大队做我现在做的事。
My brother's greatest ambition was to work up there at 51 doing what I do.
我希望我能让他看看我们在这里建造的东西。
And I wish I could have shown him what we built down here.
（喘气）
[PANTING]
你是好的。
You're okay.
只是…
Just…
试着呼吸。
Try to breathe.
好吧？
Okay?
当我弟弟和我还是孩子的时候，他们告诉我们不明飞行物只是气象气球。
When my brother and I were kids they told us that UFOs were just weather balloons.
太空垃圾。
Space trash.
库布里克在好莱坞的工作室执导了登月。
Kubrick directed the moon landing in a Hollywood studio.
很酷的故事。
Cool story.
你要去哪里？这第一个。
Where are you going? This first.
暴露的风险会增加吗？
Is there an increased risk of exposure?
我担心的不是我们。
It's not us I'm worried about.
你知道我们携带各种各样的病毒
You know we carry all kinds of viruses and.
可能对敏感生命形式有害的细菌。
bacteria that could be harmful to a sensitive lifeform.
我们不知道我们在处理什么。
And we don't know exactly what we're dealing with here.
只要我们能保证客人的安全就行。
As long as we're keeping the guests safe.
（播放音乐）
[MUSIC PLAYING]
这是我们第一次有一个宿主和我们的共生体相容。
This is the first time we've had a host compatible with one of our symbiotes.
现在我们可以和一个人说话了。
And now we'll be able to talk to one.
[音乐播放]自从我们把他绑在一起，他就一直感到恐慌。
[MUSIC PLAYING] He's been experiencing panic surges since we've bonded him.
试试jingle bells。
Try jingle bells.
所以舒缓。
So soothing.
我怎么没想到呢？
Well, why didn't I think of that?
释放他。
Release him.
嗨。
Hi.
我是佩恩医生。泰迪。
I'm Dr. Payne. Teddy.
你在这里很安全。
You're safe here.
我会帮你的。
I'm gonna help you.
你们两个。
Both of you.
转移成功了。
The transfer was successful.
我们别无选择。
We had no choice.
我们必须试着救你。
We had to try and save you.
的怪物。
The monsters.
你也坏了。
You're broken too.
（播放音乐）
[MUSIC PLAYING]
我可以……
May I…
我可以问你几个问题吗？
May I ask you some questions?
这个共生体在和你交流吗？
Is this symbiote communicating with you?
你听到了吗？
Do you hear it?
声音使它们苦恼。
Sound distresses them.
好吧。
Okay.
他们为什么在这里？
Why are they here?
他们想要什么？
What do they want?
安全的避风港。
Safe haven.
避风港？
Safe haven?
我们在跑步。
We were running.
他说的是其他共生体吗？
Is he talking about the other symbiotes?
我想是的。
I think so.
他的造物在宇宙中寻找我们。
His creatures search the universe for us.
我们会没事的。
We will be fine.
等我们到了，他会把我们都杀了。
And when we are, he will kill us all.
谁？
Who?
什么都不会留下。
There will be nothing left.
在这里吗？在地球上吗？
Here? On Earth?
他们为什么要跑？
Why were they running?
因为有黑暗，
Because there is a dark,
冰冷的海水
cold sea.
围绕着这个宇宙。
around this universe.
这是什么？
What is it?
怎么啦？
What?
你知道该怎么做。
You know what to do.
我看到了未来。
I've seen the future.
黑暗中……
The darkness…
必须离开。
has to leave.
我是机长。
This is your captain speaking.
我们目前在31000英尺的舒适高度巡航。
We are currently cruising at a comfortable 31, 000 feet.
如果你往左边看，你就会看到大峡谷。
If you look out there to your left, just now you will see the Grand Canyon.
那些是我们能找到的！
Those are we can find!
我的天啊！
Oh my God!
直飞纽约！
Direct to New York!
我的嘴好干！
My mouth is so dry!
我们还你清白！
And we clear your name!
太冷了！
It's so empressently cold!
所有那些高个女孩都这么做！
All those tall girls doing it!
他不像个小婊子一样哭诉！
He doesn't whine like a little bitch!
那是什么？
What was that?
What is that?
对不起，ana
I'm sorry, A.N.A.
但我必须消失。
But I've got to disappear.
现在该做什么？
What now?
我们有大麻烦了！
We're in deep shit!
你为什么要那样做？
Why did you do that?
我会解释的。
I will explain.
我得说这是史上最恶心的宿醉了。
I'm gonna go ahead and say that this is the shittest hangover of all time.
快看，艾迪。
Look at it, Eddie.
这不是很惊人吗？
Isn't it just astonishing?
闭嘴。
Shut up.
我想我不会的，永远住在这里。
I don't think I might, living here forever.
我们刚刚面对的是一台名副其实的死亡机器。
We just came face to face with a literal death machine.
永远似乎很乐观。
Forever seems pretty optimistic.
随着51区的退役，会不会
With the decommissioning of Area 51, will the.
五角大楼终于承认他们持有UAP了吗？
Pentagon finally admit that they've been holding UAP?
这对你来说是未知的空中现象。
That's unidentified aerial phenomena to you.
是的，爸爸，我们知道。
Yeah, Dad, we know.
因为我没机会看到谁造了这些东西。
When I wouldn't get to see who built one of those things.
所以我们才拿出积蓄来开这趟自驾游，宝贝。
That's why we cashed in our savings and came on this road trip, babe.
这样你就能看到了。
So you could finally get to see.
这是废话。
That's bullshit.
如果我是对的呢？
Yeah, well what if I'm right?
那我真希望我们不会在外星人的太空实验室里屁股上插着探测器。
Then I really hope we don't end up in an alien space lab with probes up our asses.
我们死了。
We're dead.
驴。
Asses.
[笑]
[Laughing]
踢出了一些沙砾。
Kicked up some gravel there.
紧，家人。
In tight, family.
你好吗？
You good?
太疯狂了。
That was wild.
狗吐了吗？
Did the dog vomit?
是的。
Yeah.
好吧。
Okay.
我们能行。
We've got this.
软着陆。
Soft landing.
弯曲你的膝盖。
Bend your knees.
投入你的核心。
Engage your core.
是的，是的，就是这样。
Yes, yes, that's it.
是的，就是这样。
Yes, that's it.
哇。
Whoa.
做得很好。
Well done.
太可怕了。
That was terrifying.
这里不是纽约。
This is not New York.
不，这是荒地。
No, this is a wasteland.
我发现了被动攻击。
I'm detecting passive aggression.
是吗？
Are you?
是的。
Yeah.
哦，对不起。
Oh, I'm sorry.
那么主动攻击呢？
How about some active aggression?
你刚把我从757飞机上扔下去，连
You just threw me off a 757 without even the.
从我的长期垂直的一点点考虑。
slightest consideration from my chronic vertical.
那是一架空客A320。
It was an Airbus A320.
是吗？
Was it?
我很抱歉。
I am sorry.
万岁。
Hooray.
那是什么东西？
And what was that thing?
我们刚榨汁的那个东西。
That thing that we just juiced back there.
就像这样。
Well, that's going to be like this.
不，我绝对可以保证。
No, I can absolutely guarantee that.
我不会的。
I'm not gonna.
你在干什么？
What are you doing?
你为什么要这么做？
Why are you doing that?
这很奇怪。
That's a pretty weird.
这是令人毛骨悚然的。
That's creepy.
那是一种异体生物。
That was a xenophage.
怎么啦？
What?
A xenophage.
一种共生菌。
A symbiote cantella.
当然可以。
Of course.
问题是，如果她找到了来这里的路，其他人很快就会跟上。
Problem is, if she has found her way here, others will soon follow.
其他人呢？
Others?
噬菌体的制造者也创造了一个共生体。
The xenophage's maker also created a symbiote.
那是你妹妹。
So that's your sister.
共生体背叛了他。
Oh, the symbiote's turned on him.
把他关在金塔。
Locked him up on Kinta.
你的星球。
Your planet.
不，不是你的星球。
No, not your planet.
不是你的星球。
Not your planet.
我们为他建的监狱。
The prison we built for him to sleep.
当然可以。
Of course.
友爱。
Fraternity.
那他叫什么名字？
What's his name then?
我没听见他说什么。
I didn't hear what he said.
不！
No!
这是认真的，艾迪。
This is serious, Eddie.
这不是空谈。
This is not talk.
安静。
Quiet.
这是什么，Isilom？
What is this, Isilom?
这禅的东西，反正跟你共生百要。
This zen thingy, the symbiote hundred want with you anyway.
它不？
It doesn't?
它需要我们。
It wants us.
我们确实有些东西。
We have something indeed.
我们只有这些垃圾。
We only have this shitty shit.
你有一票。
You got one vote.
一个人。
Someone.
法典。
The codex.
现在该做什么？
What now?
我示范给你看。
I'll show you.
该死的！
Damn it!
你在干什么？
What are you doing?
假设你死了。
Let's say you died.
我可以让你起死回生。
I could bring you back to life.
嗯，我喜欢这样。
Well, I like that.
但如果我做了，我们各自的生命力量
But if I did, our separate life forces.
会变成一种叫做法典的力量。
would become one single force called a codex.
法典是什么鬼东西？
What the hell is a codex?
这是一把钥匙。
It's a key.
打开笼子的钥匙。
A key that unlocks a cage.
克林塔尔的监狱。
The prison on Klyntar.
它将解放我们的造物主。
It would free our creator.
谢天谢地，我们还没死。
Well, thank God we haven't died.
是的，除了那一次。
Yeah, except that one time.
哦，不。
Oh no.
不。
No.
所以你是说我们带着这东西？
So you're telling me we're carrying this thing?
所以这个噬菌体才会追杀我们。
That's why this enophage is hunting us.
我们该怎么办？
What do we do?
只有当共生体完全成形时她才能看到法典。
She can only see the codex when a symbiote is in its full true form.
正确的。
Right.
你是说你不能出来。
You mean you can't come out.
我能做到。
I can do this.
但如果我完全变形，法典会给她发送跟踪信号。
But if I fully transform, the codex sends her a tracking signal.
她会找到我们，把它从我们脊椎里扯出来，把纳尔从克林塔尔手里救出来。
She'll find us, rip it out of our spine, and free Nal from Klyntar.
那我们要怎么摆脱这个手抄本呢？
So how do we get rid of this codex?
只要你和我都活着，法典就存在。
As long as you and I both live, the codex exists.
如果我们中的一个死了，法典也就没了。
If one of us should die, the codex will die.
这对我没用。
That's not gonna work for me.
或者我。
Or me.
这种噬菌体速度很快。
That enophage was fast.
联调局要花很长时间才能把我们和
It will take long for the feds to tie us to.
我们留在墨西哥的那四具无头尸体。
those four headless bodies we left in Mexico.
我们得离开这里。
We gotta get outta here.
是啊，我们得走了。
Yeah, we better go.
四条腿胜过一条腿。
Four legs are better than one.
跟我说实话，伙计。
Be honest with me, buddy.
你觉得你能多快让那东西跑起来而不把它弄坏？
How fast do you think you can get that thing to go without killing it?
只有一个办法能知道。
Only one way to find out.
嘘，嘘。别吓着他。
Shh, shh. Don't scare him.
别吓着她。她是你的。
Don't scare her. She was yours.
不错的马，他。
Nice horse, he.
惊喜，马，他！
Surprise, horse, he!
我爱马，他！
I love horse, he!
骑我吧，牛仔！
Ride me cowboy!
你这个混蛋！
You are an asshole!
我对天发誓，等我下马，
I swear to God, when I get off this horse,
我要揍死你，你个混蛋！
I'm gonna kick your ass, you motherfucker!
这就是马力！
Now, that's horse power!
避风港？
Safe Haven?
不。他们不是来这里避难的。
No. They're not here for a safe haven.
给现在的房客换个新家怎么样？
How about a new home to make the current tenants?
我觉得你看太多外星人入侵的电影了，雷克斯。
I think you've watched too many alien invasion movies, Rex.
有我吗？
Have I?
他们在跑。他就是这么说的。
They were running. That's what he said.
别自欺欺人了。
Don't kid yourself.
他们一直在迁徙。
They were always migrating.
一颗携带共生生物的流星坠落在地球上，它们都幸存了下来。
A meteor carrying symbiote life, crashes on Earth, and they all survive.
巧合吗？饶了我吧。
Coincidence? Give me a break.
好吧。
Alright.
我们去找他们吧。
Let's go get them.
你太不顾一切地相信他们来这里是出于无私的原因。
You're so desperate to believe that they're here for altruistic reasons.
让你变得危险。
Makes you dangerous.
（紧张的音乐）
[tense music]
我们刚截获了空中客车打来的紧急电话
We just intercepted an emergency call from an airbus out.
他说，一名男子在红杉上空跳下飞机。
of Mexico, saying a man jumped off the plane over Sequoia.
我们走osmore。
We'll take the osmore.
睁大眼睛，佩恩。
Eyes wide, Payne.
（尖叫）
[screaming]
（枪声）
[gunfire]
（呻吟）
[groaning]
我感觉不到我的蛋蛋了。
I can't feel my balls.
现在…
Now…
太可怕了。
That was horrible.
（尖叫）
[screaming]
（雷）
[thunder]
（喘气）
[gasping]
[低沉的无线电杂音]
[muffled radio chatter]
干掉他。
Take him out.
收集一个共生体。
Collect a symbiote.
[低沉的无线电杂音]
[muffled radio chatter]
（的）
[grunting]
（枪声）
[gunfire]
[低沉的无线电杂音]
[muffled radio chatter]
（枪声）（枪声）
[gunfire] [gunfire]
[低沉的无线电杂音]
[muffled radio chatter]
（枪声）
[gunfire]
[低沉的无线电杂音][雷声]
[muffled radio chatter] [thunder]
（的）
[grunting]
（枪声）
[gunfire]
[低沉的无线电杂音]
[muffled radio chatter]
（喘气）
[gasping]
（发出）
[squeaking]
[低沉的无线电杂音]
[muffled radio chatter]
[低沉的无线电杂音][敲门声]
[muffled radio chatter] [knocking]
（的）
[grunting]
[低沉的无线电杂音]
[muffled radio chatter]
（枪）
[gunshot]
（喘气）
[gasping]
[panting]
（喘气）
[gasping]
（水溅）
[water splashing]
（的）
[grunting]
（水溅）
[water splashing]
（的）
[grunting]
（喘气）
[gasping]
（水溅）
[water splashing]
（的）
[grunting]
不，是法典！
No, the Codex!
不让你死！
Not let you die!
（咯咯笑）
[gurgling]
（尖叫）
[screaming]
（咯咯笑）
[gurgling]
（咯咯笑）（咯咯笑）
[gurgling] [gurgling]
（咯咯笑）
[gurgling]
这是怎么来的？
Where did that come from?
（咯咯笑）
[gurgling]
莫斯！咖啡！
Moss! Coffee!
（咯咯笑）
[gurgling]
（的）
[grunting]
（水溅）
[water splashing]
（咯咯笑）
[gurgling]
该走了！地狱耶！
Time to go! Hell yeah!
（咯咯笑）
[gurgling]
（的）
[grunting]
（尖叫）
[screaming]
（咯咯笑）
[gurgling]
（水溅）
[water splashing]
（的）
[grunting]
（咆哮）
[growling]
（咯咯笑）
[gurgling]
发生了什么事？
What happened?
外面还有别的东西。别的吗？
There's something else out here. Something else?
他说这会发生。我刚失去了三个人。
He said this would happen. I just lost three people.
你能收集样品吗？
Can you collect any samples?
样本。
Samples.
（门）
[door opens]
（门关闭）
[door closes]
（风）
[wind blowing]
（小鸟喳喳叫）
[birds chirping]
他们不是联邦探员。那些都是特种部队干的。
Those were not Feds. Those were some special forces shit.
他们想杀了我们。是的。是的，很好。
They were trying to kill us. Yeah. Yeah, great.
太好了。所以现在我们有了警察。
Great. So now we have the cops.
美国军队和地狱来的怪物在追杀我们。
The United States Army and some creature from hell hunting us.
天啊，我刚看到一个外星人的脸后面喷着血。
Oh, God, I just saw blood in a spray out of the back of an alien's face.
他们杀了人。
They killed someone.
他们没给你选择。
They didn't give you a choice.
你没给我选择的机会。我找不到你。
You didn't give me a choice. I couldn't get to you.
一年前你偷走了我的生活。
It's a year ago when you stole my life.
我们在一起一年了。
We've been together for a whole year.
一年太长了。在我们到达纽约之前躲好，别被杀。
A year too long. Just stay hidden while we get to New York without getting killed.
（咯咯笑）
[gurgling]
【砰】
[thud]
我们需要你出来。
We need you to come out.
你说的那个东西，那个生物……
The thing you talked about, the creature…
这里的。
It's here.
它杀死了一些人。
It killed some people.
（水溅）
[water splashing]
（发声）
[hissing]
（喘息）
[gasps]
（发声）
[hissing]
将……
Will…
是如此美丽。
is so beautiful.
（发声）
[hissing]
我感觉……
I sense…
我感觉到了我的旧的。
I sense my old one.
然而，那个诺泄密的人却不在这里。
And yet, the one Nolceaks is not here.
（发声）
[hissing]
他在寻找什么？
What does he seek?
黑色的那个。
The Black One.
黑色的那个？
The Black One?
Voxymbia吗？
Voxymbia?
他是唯一带着法典的人。
He's the only one who carries a Codex.
结束……
The end…
是现在。
is now.
（发声）
[hissing]
你需要你的西装。
You need your suit.
还在担心这玩意会感冒吗？
Still worried about giving this thing a cold?
“毒液”是诺丝重获自由的关键。
Venom carries the key to Nolce's freedom.
永远不要得到它。
Never obtain it.
否则你的种族将被消灭。
Or your race will be killed.
你……
You…
和你……
and you…
和…
and…
你……
you…
每个人，一切。
everyone, everything.
我们怎么阻止上面的东西下来呢？
How do we stop whatever's up there from coming down here?
你不能。
You can't.
他比宇宙还老。
He's older than the universe.
他指的是钥匙。
He means the key.
然后一切都会结束。
Then everything will end.
我们怎么才能阻止他得到它？
How do we stop him from getting it?
如果共生体和宿主都活着，
If the symbiote and the host are alive,
那么古抄本还活着。
then the Codex is alive.
如果其中一个死了呢？
And if one of them dies?
法典死了？
The Codex dies?
法典死了。
The Codex dies.
雷克斯，你不是认真的吧。
Rex, you can't be serious.
哦，我愿意。
Oh, I'm game.
毁掉法典是唯一无法获得它的方法。
Destroying the Codex is the only way it remains unobtainable.
对吧？
Right?
伙计，我在跟你说话呢。
Hey, buddy, I'm talking to you.
破坏吗？
Destroying it?
我们甚至还没有触及表面。
We have barely even scratched the surface.
我的人都死了。
My people are dead.
不可战胜的力量即将到来。
Something is coming that cannot be beaten.
我要马上停止这一切。
I'm stopping all this shit right now.
科学就是牺牲。
Science is sacrifice.
泰迪。
Teddy.
是认真的。听她的。
Is serious. Listen to her.
（门）
[door opens]
你最近和家人说过话吗？
Have you spoken to your family recently?
一切都还好吗？
Is everything okay?
是的。
Yeah.
我闻到了湿狗的味道，酱汁冒了出来。
I smell wet dog and sauce emerges.
嘿，friendo。你没事吧？
Hey, friendo. You okay there?
不，我不好。外面蛮野的。
No, I'm not okay. It's pretty wild out there.
我知道。你饿了吗？
I know. You hungry?
是的。
Yes.
过来。
Come over.
谢谢你！
Thank you.
这是我妻子，诺瓦·穆恩。
Well, this is my wife, Nova Moon.
嗨。
Hi.
这些是我的孩子，Echo和Leaf。
And these are my kids, Echo and Leaf.
一生都在接受治疗。
A lifetime in therapy.
不喜欢。
Don't.
你敢。
Don't you dare.
哇，你的孩子多漂亮啊？
Wow, how beautiful are your children?
这就是Blue。
And that's Blue.
谁是狗？
Who is a dog?
我是马丁。
And I'm Martin.
嗨，马丁。
Hey, Martin.
嘿。
Hey.
我是埃迪。
I'm Eddie.
很高兴认识你，埃迪。
Nice to meet you, Eddie.
你也一样。快乐。
You too. Pleasure.
请坐。
Come sit, please.
好吧。
Okay.
来吧，谢谢。
Come on, thank you.
耶稣基督。
Jesus Christ.
所以，正确的。
So, right.
那盘合十礼上没死人吗，伙计？
Oh, so nothing died on that plate namaste, man?
谢谢你！
Thank you.
帮助，小胡子！
Help, Tash!
哦，亲爱的。
Oh, dear.
艾迪，你要去哪里？
Eddie, where are you headed?
纽约。
New York.
哦，哇。
Oh, wow.
好吧。
Yeah, all right.
去纽约的路很远。我们是裸虾，伙计。
Long way to New York. We're naked shrimps, man.
是的。
Yeah.
我们可以骑你去维加斯。
We could ride you out to Vegas.
是的。
Yeah.
这些人很奇怪。我告诉你。
These people are weird. I'm telling you.
那真是太好了。谢谢你！
That would be so kind. Thank you.
不客气。
You're welcome.
当然可以。生活是一场大冒险。
Of course. Life's one big adventure.
谁不喜欢交新朋友呢？
Who doesn't love making new friends?
对吧？
Right?
这家伙真是个连环杀手
This guy is so one of those serial killer hitchhikers.
来自我最喜欢的谋杀播客。
from my favorite murder podcast.
宝贝，现在不是时候。
Baby, not now.
社会服务机构还没把我们带走。
That was social services not taking us away yet.
她是在开玩笑。
She's joking.
我不是。
I'm not.
请，亲爱的。
Please, honey.
所以我们在外星高速公路上行驶。
So we're riding the extraterrestrial highway.
是的。
Yep.
看我。是谁？
Watch me. Who is it?
这条路通往51区。
It's the road that leads to Area 51.
看看我们能不能在他们永远关闭这里之前认出外星人来？
See if we can spot as an alien before they shut the place down forever, you know?
这是我一生的梦想。
It's my lifelong dream.
我们现在就可以给他看。
We can show him right now.
不相信？
Not a believer?
马丁，我该怎么说呢？
Actually, Martin, how do I put this?
我是。
I am.
哦。
Oh.
这就是“我是我的忠实信徒”。
That's the I am I big, big believer.
你没那么大。
You're not that big.
哦，有你就够了。
Oh, and you can be enough.
实际上，我在it部门工作
And actually, I was in I.T.
是你吗？
Were you?
是的。
Yeah.
太酷了。
That's so cool.
谢谢。
Thanks.
我希望你不要失望，知道吗？
I hope you don't get disappointed, you know?
我希望如果你真的找到了，我希望你遇到一个真正好的外星人。
And I hope that if you do find one, I hope you meet a really good alien.
还不错。
Not a bad one.
是的。
Yeah.
我能分辨出黑暗力量，埃迪。
I know a dark force when I see one, Eddie.
这里有点热。
It's kind of hot in here.
你会习惯的。
You get used to it.
你知道空调对你的健康不好。
A.C. is really bad for your health, you know.
好吧。
All right.
家人准备好了吗？
Family ready?
是的。
Yep.
客人准备好了。
Guest ready.
让我们震撼这个露营车。
Let's rock this camper.
地面控制呼叫汤姆少校。
Ground control to Major Tom.
哦，我喜欢合唱。
Oh, I love a sing-along.
地面控制呼叫汤姆少校。
Ground control to Major Tom.
朝我脸上开枪。
Shoot me in the face.
吃蛋白质药片，戴上头盔。
Take your protein pills and put your helmet on.
哦，是的。
Oh, yeah.
这是我的果酱。
This is my jam.
九个。
Nine.
八个。
Eight.
七。
Seven.
六。
Six.
启动复合发动机。
Commencing compound engines on.
三。
Three.
两个。
Two.
看看吧。
Check it out.
一个。
One.
让上帝的爱在椽子上。
And make God's love be in the rafter.
来吧，艾迪，跟着唱。
Come on, Eddie, sing along.
我很好。
I'm good.
你在这个世界上吗？
Are you in the world?
不。就当这是观光巴士吧。
No. Just think of this as the tour bus.
我们是乐队，你可以是粉丝。
We're the band, and you could be the groupie.
来吧。
Come on.
不要太死板。
Don't be square.
别让我开口。
Don't get me started.
这是汤姆少校的地面控制中心。
This is Major Tom's ground control.
我要进门了。
I'm stepping through the door.
我正以最奇特的方式漂浮着。
And I'm floating in the most peculiar way.
小心点，今天的星星看起来很不一样。
Care up, and the stars look very different today.
为什么？
Why?
因为他是我锡罐里的城市。
For he is my city in a tin can.
可以做罐头！
Can make a tin!
远在世界之上。
Far above the world.
就像洗澡一样。
Like a bath, already.
地球是蓝色的，我什么也做不了。
Planet Earth is blue, and there's nothing I can do.
不。
No.
地面控制呼叫汤姆少校。
This is ground control to Major Tom.
有时候我想，如果我们过这样的生活，我们会更幸福。
Sometimes I think we would have been happier with a life like this.
球员们也想知道，对吧？
And the players want to know, shall we?
是的。
Yeah.
现在有迹象表明几天内会有现金。
Now the signs lead to cash for a few days.
我的爱。
My love.
汤姆少校呼叫地面控制中心。
This is Major Tom to ground control.
我要进门了。
I'm stepping through the door.
我正以一种最奇特的方式漂浮着。
And I'm floating in a most peculiar way.
今天的星星看起来很不一样。
And the stars look very different today.
因为他是我锡罐里的城市。
For he is my city in a tin can.
远在世界之上。
Far above the world.
（处理）
(crunching)
你喜欢巧克力吗？
You like chocolate?
嘘，他们不让我们吃糖。
Shh, they don't let us eat sugar.
他们不？
They don't?
我有个朋友很喜欢巧克力。
I have a friend who loves chocolate.
谢谢你！
Thank you.
你真是太好了。
It's very kind of you.
我不想看到洋葱。
I don't wanna see an onion.
你不？
You don't?
可怕的。
Scary.
好吧。
Okay.
你知道，害怕是正常的。
Well, you know, it's okay to be scared.
我很害怕。
I'm scared.
我经常去。
Like, I go all the time.
保证我不跟任何人见面？
Promise I won't see anyone?
朋友。
Buddy.
外星人不是真的，好吗？
Aliens are not real, okay?
的承诺。
Promise.
好吧。
Okay.
你说得对。
You said the right thing.
你会是个好爸爸的。
You would make a good dad.
我们走了很长一段路，你和我。
We've come a long way, you and me.
我们还有很多路要走，巴迪。
We have many more roads to travel, Buddy.
那不是很好吗？
Wouldn't that be nice?
你说什么？
You say something?
不，我想只是在做梦。
No, just dream in, I guess.
那是附近的丽卡。
That's the near Rika.
莉香附近吗？
Near Rika?
是的。
Yeah.
在我们的心中有一扇门
There's a doorway in our minds.
这通常是保密的
that usually remains hidden in secret.
直到死亡时间
until the time of death.
世界上有很多疯狂的事，埃迪。
Crazy things in this world, Eddie.
如果你开门的话，你可以看到他们。
You can see them if you're open.
哦，我看到了。
Oh, I seen them.
我很高兴我们没吃这么好吃的，家人。
I'm glad we didn't eat this fine, family.
（欢快的音乐）
(upbeat music)
欢迎来到第二次机会之城。
Welcome to the city of Second chances.
哇。
Whoa.
（欢快的音乐）
(upbeat music)
谢谢你！
Thank you.
在这里，朋友。
Here, buddy.
谢谢你！
Thank you.
保持蓝色，保持。
Stay blue, stay.
谢谢你！
Thank you.
好吧，蓝色的。
Okay, blue.
拉斯维加斯。
Vegas.
听着，我只想把这个给你。
Listen, I just want you to have this.
请。
Please.
谢谢你！
Thank you.
优质支撑，缓冲。
Quality support, cushioning.
此外，它们还配有抗菌脚垫。
Plus, they come with an anti-microbial footbed.
不，拒绝他们。
No, reject them.
黄蜂卡车。
Wasp the trucks.
谢谢你！
Thank you.
哦，宝贝，宝贝，这是个狂野的世界
Oh, baby, baby, it's a wild world.
但我会永远记得你
But I'll always remember you.
再见，马丁。
Goodbye, Martin.
再见了。
It's goodbye for now.
我也这么想，艾迪。
That's what I like to think, Eddie.
好吧，再见。
Okay, bye.
嗨，马丁。
Hey, Martin.
那个门口，丽卡附近的那个？
That doorway, the near Rika?
是的，是开着的。
Yeah, it's open.
我做了什么？
Do I?
注意安全。
Just be safe.
好吧。
Okay.
谢谢。
Thanks.
哦，耶稣。
Oh, Jesus.
怎么啦？
What?
嗯，这是有史以来的最低点。
Well, this is an all-time low.
你有巧克力。
You have chocolate.
Yum！
Yum!
哦，哦，哦。
Oh, oh, oh.
我想在我们去纽约的时候见到她，埃迪。
I would like to see her where we get to New York, Eddie.
你知道，她是用来欢迎访客的
You know, she was built to welcome visitors.
去美国吧，伙计。
to America, buddy.
这是你的。
That's you.
你这么认为吗，艾迪？
You think so, Eddie?
哦，是的，我知道。
Oh yeah, I know so.
等我们离开这烂摊子，我们就去见她。
When we get out of this mess, we're gonna go see her.
我们要说，“嗨，自由女神。”
We're gonna say, "Hi, Lady Liberty."
去看她的百老汇演出！
And see her Broadway show!
是的，当然。
Yeah, sure.
哇！
Wow!
我知道你有多讨厌音乐剧。
I know how much you hate musicals.
是的，看起来会很棒的。
Yeah, it's gonna look great.
接下来是什么，西尔玛？
What's next, Thelma?
露易丝，我不确定20美元
Well, Louise, I'm not sure $20.
会给我们带来很多汽车运输的麻烦。
is gonna get us much in the way of motor transport.
但我再也不会骑外星马了。
But I'm not ever riding an alien horse again.
看来我们是在偷车。
So I guess it looks like we're stealing cars.
不，我看过《雨人》
No, I've watched Rain Man.
以我作为天神的无限智慧，
and in my infinite wisdom as a celestial being,
操作这个系统很容易。
working the system is easy.
你先玩老虎机，然后是二十一点，然后是轮盘赌，
You hit the slots, then blackjack, then roulette,
宾果，邦戈，豪华车，蓝牙音响系统，
bingo, bango, luxury ride, Bluetooth sound system,
赛车，和顶部向下。
racing, and the top down.
因为这就是我们做事的方式。
Because that's how we roll.
哈里斯赌场有严格的着装要求。
Harris Casino has a strict dress code.
不，你知道吗？
No, you know what?
这是一家旅馆。
It's a hotel.
这些是我的度假服装。
These are my vacation clothes.
你们是更好的。
You're better ones.
他没有错。
He's not wrong.
看看你。
Look at you.
不，别逼我，好吗，伙计？
No, don't push it, all right, buddy?
需要帮忙吗？
Want a hand?
是的。
Yes.
我就是这样，把他打晕了。
That did me, knock him out.
你在干什么？
What are you doing?
他是个混蛋。
He was being a dick.
是的，我是。
Yeah, I was.
噢，看。
Oh, look.
我们需要伪装一下。
We need a disguise.
我们在做什么？
What are we doing?
嘿，嘿，伙计。
Hey, hey man.
嗨。
Hi.
哦，上帝。
Oh, God.
哇。
Whoa.
你为什么总是把人搞得神魂颠倒？
Why do you keep rocking people out?
你怎么了？
What is wrong with you?
怎么啦？
What?
很抱歉，伙计。
So sorry, buddy.
我真的很抱歉。
I am so, so sorry.
嘿，你是我的宝贝。
Hey there, you're my baby.
现在没人会认出我们了。
Now no one will recognize us.
认真对待。
Seriously.
你可能会被选为年度最性感男人。
You could get voted people's sexiest man of the year.
如果还有人在乎你是谁。
If anyone cared who you are anymore.
我以前得过性感男人奖。
I've won sexy man awards before.
你当然有。
Of course you have.
嘿，嘿。
Hey, hey.
那个做这件事的人，
The guy that did that,
抱歉，他在那边的拱门里。
sorry, he's in the arched over there.
他雀跃。
He shitfaced.
你们是坏人。
You're bad people.
是的，我们是。
Yeah, we are.
顺便说一下，他的鞋子我们留着。
We're keeping his shoes, by the way.
我们很有钱，我们知道这一点。
We are so money and we know it.
欢迎来到巴黎。
Welcome to the Paris.
谢谢你！
Thank you.
不，谢谢。
No, thank you.
宝贝，我在这里
Baby, here I am.
我是现场的人
I'm a man on the scene.
我可以给你你想要的
I can give you what you want.
但你得跟我回家
But you got to go home with me.
我忘记了一些美好的旧爱
I forgot some good old lovin'
我得到了一些阳光和黄金
And I got some sun and gold.
哦，是的！
Oh, yes!
把20乘起来。
Let me multiply the 20.
让我用四倍火力。
Let me quadruple-fire it.
你在干什么？
What are you doing?
不，这是我们所有的钱了。
No, this is all the money that we have.
今晚去找你的女人吧！
Look for your lady tonight!
时髦的夹克！
Snazzy jacket!
我们把它吃光，然后偷来吧。
Let's eat up and steal it.
我知道今晚幸运女神站在我们这边！
I know Lady Luck is on our side tonight!
不，我觉得是幸运女神
No, I would say that Lady Luck.
今晚绝对不会站在你这边。
is definitely not on your side tonight.
但我甚至想说，幸运女神
But I would even go so far to say that Lady Luck.
讨厌你，伙计。
hates you, buddy.
我现在停不下来了！
I can't stop now!
你当然停不下来。
Of course you can't stop.
这是什么感觉？
What is this feeling?
就像——这种感觉？
It's like… This feeling?
哈！
Ha!
好像我所有的问题都消失了！
It's like all of my problems have gone away!
一直这样做。
Do this all the time.
埃罗尔，我需要更多的钱。
Errol, I need more money.
但我们没钱了，伙计。
But we don't have any more money, buddy.
上帝！
God!
上帝保佑！
God bless!
你是个输不起的人。
You are a sore loser.
是的，先生，它是！
Yes, sir, it is!
哦！
Oh!
我想你把我的脚弄断了。
I think you broke my foot.
天啊，幸运女神真是个善变的荡妇！
God, Lady Luck is a fickle slut!
哦。
Oh.
我们应该玩那台机器！
We should have played that machine!
是的，是的，是的！
Yes, yes, yes!
不，等等！
No, F-ing, wait!
埃迪，兄弟！
Eddie, bro!
陈太太！
Mrs. Chen!
哦，不，不，不！
Oh, no, no, no!
陈先生，我是陈太太！
Mr. Chen, it's Mrs. Chen!
噢，陈太太！
Oh, Mrs. Chen!
埃迪，谢谢！
Eddie, please!
陈太太，陈太太！
Mrs. Chen, Mrs. Chen!
我要哭了！
I'm gonna cry!
我也是。
Me too.
哇，你怎么了？
Wow, what happened to you?
你看起来很性感！
You look hot!
你也是。
So do you.
真的很热。
Really hot.
我总是看起来很性感。
I always look hot.
是的。
Yeah.
里面有个大个子吗？
Is a big guy in there?
是的。
Yeah.
你喜欢我的衣服吗？
Do you like my dress?
我穿的太大了
I've been wearing so big,
他们在服装店给了我信用额度，
they gave me a credit line at the clothes store,
然后是顶层套房。
and then the penthouse suite.
你知道这套西装是我偷的
Wow, you know I stole this suit.
一个在我身上撒尿的人。
of a guy who pissed on me.
我把他打晕了，把他丢在灌木丛里。
I knocked him out, I left him in a bush.
这就解释了臭味。
Well, that explained a stink.
你可以用我的房间打扫，
You could use my room to clean up,
然后我们——
and then we…
心痛。
Heartache.
哦，那太好了。
Oh, that would be so good.
还有客房服务。
And room service.
（女人尖叫）
(woman screams)
我们抓到他了。
We got him.
布洛克在拉斯维加斯的巴黎酒店的闭路电视上发现了身份。
Positive ID on Brock's CCTV hit the Paris Hotel, Vegas.
我们重组了六人组吗？
Have we reconstituted the six?
是的，先生。
Yes, sir.
把他放进去。
Put him in.
六个人在路上了。
The six are on route.
他们会把他带进来的。
They'll bring him in.
但这次我要求控制
But this time I'm requesting control.
帝国计划的一部分。
of the Imperium program.
我允许你这么做，将军。
You have my permission, General.
当雷声轰鸣，
When thunder roars,
它咆哮着，
and it roars,
它咆哮着。
and it roars.
（不祥的音乐）
(ominous music)
让我们跳舞吧，宝贝。
Let's dance, baby.
是的，我喜欢跳舞。
Yeah, I love dances.
请吃吧，那东西会找到我们的。
Please eat that thing will find us.
不要扫别人的兴。
Don't be a party pooper.
不，不要鼓励他。
No, do not encourage him.
你知道吗，陈先生，我们是逃犯。
You know what, Mr. Chen, we are fugitives.
我们在逃亡中，谢谢你们的邀请。
We are on the run, so thank you for having us.
我们得走了。
We gotta go.
你真没意思。
You're no fun.
走之前再跳最后一支舞。
One last dance before you go.
我们从来不做我想做的事。
We never do anything I want to do.
只是一个小舞蹈。
Just a little dance.
然后你放弃了。
And you gave up.
把我的鸡带走。
Away my chickens.
陈太太，我们绕场吧。
Let's cut around, Mrs. Chen.
我放弃了。
I give up.
哦，不，我无法忘记。
Oh no, I cannot unsee that.
我无法忽视这一点。
I cannot unsee that.
（欢快的音乐）
(upbeat music)
你可以跳舞。
You can dance.
享受人生中最美好的时光。
Having the time of your life.
你们俩什么时候练的？
When did you two practice this?
（叹息）
(sighs)
（欢快的音乐）
(upbeat music)
该死的！
God damn it!
我告诉过你会发生这种事。
I told you this would happen.
（尖叫）
(screams)
别慌，她看不到库德克斯。
Don't panic, she can't see the kudex.
那是什么鬼东西？
What the hell is that?
哇，好丑。
Wow, so ugly.
呆在你能呆的地方。
Stay where you can.
她看不见她要找的东西。
She can't see the thing she's looking for.
（尖叫）
(screams)
哦！
Oh!
不管怎样你都活着！
You live anyhow!
我选择。
I choose.
（悬疑的音乐）
(suspenseful music)
哇。
Wow.
（笑）
(laughs)
51区。
Area 51.
是的。
Yeah.
嗯？
Huh?
是的。
Yeah.
我们成功了。
We made it.
你终于看到了，丹。
You finally got to see it, Den.
这挺酷的。
It's kind of cool.
嗯。
Huh.
我猜。
I guess.
是的。
Yeah.
叶子。
Leaf.
亲爱的，你要去哪里？
Where you going, hon?
看看能不能找点更酷的。
Well, let's see if we can't find us something cooler.
来吧。
Come on.
来吧，伙计们。
Come on, guys.
好的，宝贝。
Okay, babe.
一生的梦想。
Life's long dream.
好了，快，快，快，快！
All right, go, go, go, go, go!
我闻起来像外星人。
I smell alien.
（笑）（悬疑的音乐）
(laughs) (suspenseful music)
没有宿主，他的情况正在恶化。
He's deteriorating without his host.
可怜的东西。
Poor thing.
把他和其他人放在下面。
Put him below with the others.
我在那里更安全。
I'm safer there.
（悬疑的音乐）
(suspenseful music)
（普通员工）
(grunts)
下来，下来。
Down, down.
加油！加油。
Come on, come on.
好吧。
All right.
嘿，嘿，嘿，嘿，嘿。
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
我想我们在上面会看得更清楚。
I think we're gonna get a better view from up there.
跟我来，伙计们，来吧。
Follow me, guys, and come on.
这太令人兴奋了。
This is so exciting.
真不敢相信我们来了。
I can't believe we're here.
哇。
Wow.
Whoa.
哦，好吧。
Oh, well.
这是什么？
What is this?
（悬疑的音乐）
(suspenseful music)
都坏了。
It's all broken.
很伤心。
So sad.
哦，老兄。
Oh, buddy.
嘿，哥们。
Hey, buddy.
哦，不。
Oh, no.
不。
No.
不，你一天能有几个小时？
Oh, no, how many hours can you have in one day?
埃迪？
Eddie?
喂？
Hello?
他们这样对我。
They did this to me.
（悬疑的音乐）
(suspenseful music)
摩根？
Morgan?
怎么啦？
What?
你还活着吗？
You're alive?
你在这里做什么？
What are you doing here?
我们被追杀了，艾迪。
We're being hunted, Eddie.
你有他需要的东西。
You have what he needs.
保护法典不受黑暗之手的侵害。
Protect the Codex from dark hands.
共生大军在这里等着。
A symbiote army waits here.
免费的。
Free them.
保护，埃迪。
Protected, Eddie.
现在必须锁起来。
Now must stay locked away.
艾迪，我是佩恩医生。
Eddie, I'm Dr. Payne.
我的朋友呢？
Where's my friend?
他现在很安全。
He's safe for now.
伟大的新闻。
Great news.
我们都做完了。
We're all done here.
这一切都不是你能控制的。
All of this is out of your hands.
这是我的实验室。
This is my lab.
不不不，不是你的。
No, no, no, not yours.
你只是在这里工作。
You just work here.
或者你做了。
Or you did.
你，圣诞老人，你要回家了。
You, Christmas, you're going home.
那他们呢？
And what about them?
你听到上面说的了。
You heard what it said.
只有他们都活着，法典才会存在。
The Codex only exists if they're both alive.
是的，我们没事，我们没事。
Yeah, we're good, we're good.
你杀了我的人。
You killed one of my people.
我要亲自回报你。
I'm returning the favor personally.
请把佩恩博士送出去。
Please escort Dr. Payne out here.
圣诞节，该走了。
Christmas, time to go.
嘿！
Hey!
（咆哮）
(growling)
大错误。
Big mistake.
（的）
(grunting)
（咆哮）
(growling)
火！
Fire!
快跑！
Run!
火！
Fire!
（咆哮）（叫喊）（枪声）
(growling) (yelling) (gunshots)
（咆哮）
(growling)
（枪声）
(gunshots)
毒液，快跑，快跑！
Venom, run, go!
（喊）
(yelling)
释放共生体。
Release the symbiotes.
（喊）
(yelling)
（枪声）
(gunshots)
（喊）
(yelling)
（的）
(grunting)
（咆哮）
(growling)
（喊）
(yelling)
（枪声）（喊叫声）（喊叫声）
(gunshots) (yelling) (yelling)
吉姆！
Jim!
（咆哮）
(growling)
拒绝她！
Turn her down!
得到她！
Get her!
（咆哮）
(growling)
走吧，孩子。
Let's go, boy.
拿下她！
Take her down!
（咆哮）
(growling)
（喊）
(yelling)
我要摔倒了！
I'm gonna fall down!
（喊）
(yelling)
的帮助！
Help!
（咆哮）
(growling)
来吧！
Come on!
（咆哮）
(growling)
离开她！
Leave her!
把大麻拿出去！
Get the clonax outta here!
（咆哮）
(growling)
这是我们的出路。
That's our way out.
（咆哮）
(growling)
（枪声）
(gunshots)
你带我们出去！
You break us out of here!
（咆哮）
(growling)
这里没有外星人，孩子们。
There's no aliens here, kids.
最好的鞋子！
Best shoes ever!
哇！
Whoa!
那是什么？
What was that?
（枪声）
(gunshots)
我们得走了，快走！
We gotta go, move it!
（咆哮）
(growling)
我们要走了！
We are leaving!
动！
Move!
动，动！
Move, move!
没事的，没事的，孩子们。
It's all right, it's all right, kids.
外星人！
Aliens!
外星人入侵！
Alien invasion!
外星人攻击！
Alien attack!
草泥马！
Motherfucker!
（咆哮）
(growling)
你们两个，出去，上帝！
You two, get out, Lord!
嘿，等等，先生，抓住我！
Hey, wait, sir, hold me!
你在空中飘飘欲仙！
You're high on the airborne!
快，快，快！
Move, move, move!
在港湾的海湾里！
In the harbor's gulf!
我们得把手抄本弄得越远越好。
We got to get the codex as far away as possible.
（咆哮）
(growling)
埃迪？
It's Eddie?
埃迪。
It's Eddie.
艾迪！
Eddie!
哦，不，埃迪，埃迪！
Oh no, Eddie, Eddie!
马丁，我是家人！
Martin, I'm family!
不能在这儿，马丁。
Can't be here, Martin.
黑暗力量，伙计！
Dark forces, man!
（咆哮）
(growling)
里奇，你能帮帮我们吗？
Ricky, can you help us?
我说谎了。
I lied.
外星人是真的。
Aliens are real.
我在这个世界上最好的朋友就是一只。
My best friend in the whole world is one.
他会带你出去的，好吗？
He's gonna get you out of here, okay?
不要害怕。
Don't be scared.
嗨。
Hi.
很高兴认识你。
Pleasure to meet you.
嗯？
Huh?
这是为了巧克力。
It's for the chocolate.
不客气。
You're welcome.
（咆哮）
(growling)
不！
No!
（尖叫）
(screaming)
坚持住，卡莉！
Hold on, Kari!
（尖叫）
(screaming)
他是想保护你。
He was trying to protect you.
我们不是坏人！
We are not the bad guys!
埃塞尔！
Ethel!
我的宝贝，我的宝贝。
My baby, my baby.
谢谢你，埃迪。
Thank you, Eddie.
不客气。
You're welcome.
你在开玩笑吧。
You gotta be kidding me.
进入！
Get in!
哇，哇！
Whoa, whoa!
滚出去！
Get out!
停！
Stop!
嘿！
Hey!
来吧。
Come on.
打电话，把法典拿来。
Call, bring me that Codex.
那是什么声音？
What's that noise?
她找到了家。
She found home.
（咆哮）
(growling)
哦，狗屎。
Oh, shit.
（尖叫）
(screaming)
滚出去！
Get out!
Get out of here!
滚出去！
注意隐蔽！”
Take cover!
我抓住你了。
I got you.
（尖叫）
(screaming)
她救了我们。
She saved us.
我没看到有什么能分散他们的注意力。
I saw no one thing that's gonna distract them.
副本。
Copy.
回到他们的车上去！
Get back to their van!
来吧！
Come on!
Kari，Kari！
Kari, Kari!
我要把他们抓起来。
I'm gonna round them up.
让直升机跟我来。
Have the chopper follow me.
快，快，快！
Go, go, go!
走吧！
Go!
（咆哮）
(growling)
走吧！
Go!
他在带他们去杀人箱。
He's leading them to a kill box.
当你得到一个锁，蒸发他们！
When you get a lock, vaporize them!
（枪声）
(gunfire)
狗屎！
Shit!
（尖叫）
(screaming)
我们回来。
We're back.
好了，好了，等等。
Okay, okay, hold it.
加油，孩子们。
Come on, kids.
加油，加油！
Go, come on!
Kari，亲爱的。
Kari, honey.
谢谢你！
Thank you.
外星人吸！
Aliens suck!
（咆哮）
(growling)
把它们点着！
Light them up!
收到。
Copy that.
扭矩消除。
Torque eliminate.
（咆哮）
(growling)
汤普森下来！
Thompson down!
它下来了，快！
It's coming down, go!
（咆哮）
(growling)
（尖叫）
(screaming)
（咆哮）
(growling)
近了！
Close!
我来做！
I'll do it!
让我们结束这一切。
Let's finish this.
与快乐。
With pleasure.
直升机的叶片。
The chopper blades.
（咆哮）
(growling)
我抓住你了。
I got you.
把他带到安全的地方。
Get him somewhere safe.
哦男孩。
Oh boy.
（咆哮）
(growling)
我很抱歉。
I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry.
好吧，好吧。
Okay, okay.
（咆哮）
(growling)
不。
No.
继续。
Go on.
好吧，好吧。
Okay, okay.
还活在你哥哥的梦里。
Still living your brother's dream.
（咆哮）
(growling)
我来了。
I'm coming.
快过来！
Get over here!
走，走！
Go, go!
（咆哮）
(growling)
我为你骄傲，埃迪。
I'm proud of you, Eddie.
都是你自己做的。
You did it all yourself.
嗯，一部分吧。
Well, some of it.
（咆哮）
(growling)
我真的很想见到她。
I really would have liked to have seen her.
谁？
Who?
自由女神。
Lady Liberty.
噢，是的。
Oh yeah.
好吧，我们要走了。
Yeah, well, we're going.
我们一离开这里就去。
We're gonna go just as soon as we get out of here.
他们会一直来的。
They're just going to keep coming.
我们永远不会离开这个地方，朋友。
We'll never leave this place, friend.
哦，上帝。
Oh God.
我们还活着。
We were alive.
我以为我们会成为致命的守护者。
I thought we were gonna be the lethal protector.
我们是来旅游的。
We are.
这就是它。
That's what this is.
是的。（戏剧性的音乐）
Yeah. (dramatic music)
好吧。
All right.
（咆哮）
(growling)
再来吧，我们。
Come again, us.
（咆哮）
(growling)
（咆哮）（咆哮）
(growling) (growling)
（咆哮）（喘气）
(growling) (panting)
（咆哮）
(growling)
（咆哮）（喘气）
(growling) (panting)
（咆哮）
(growling)
走了。
Go.
我的天啊。
Oh my God.
（咆哮）
(growling)
你在干什么？
What are you doing?
我永远不会忘记你。
I'll never forget you.
也别忘了我，埃迪。
Don't forget me, either, Eddie.
不。
No.
该走了。
Time to go.
斯特里克兰。
Strickland.
斯特里克兰授权。
Strickland authorized.
不。
No.
哦，上帝。
Oh God.
斯特里克兰。
Strickland.
斯特里克兰授权。
Strickland authorized.
（咆哮）
(growling)
哦。
Oh.
嗯？
Huh?
这只是暂时的。
It's just by for now.
（咆哮）
(growling)
（咆哮）（咆哮）（咆哮）
(growling) (growling) (growling)
不。
No.
不，不。
No, no.
（咆哮）
(growling)
不。
No.
（咆哮）
(growling)
不，埃迪。
No, Eddie.
（哭）
(crying)
（咆哮）
(growling)
（哭）
(crying)
Nureka.
（咆哮）
(growling)
嘿，哥们。
Hey, buddy.
我刚刚做了一个疯狂的梦。
I just had a crazy dream.
朋友。
Buddy.
他不会回来了。
He's not coming back.
他要回来了。
He's coming back.
但我需要他回来。
But I need him back.
他不适合这个地方。
He wasn't meant for this place.
你不可能留住他。
You couldn't have kept him.
他也不可能留住你。
And he couldn't have kept you.
对于你们的勇敢，我衷心感谢你们俩
For your bravery, you both have the heartfelt thanks.
一个感恩的国家。
of a grateful nation.
埃迪，你可以重新开始你的生活了。
Eddie, you're free to start your life again.
在旧金山发生的一切
Everything that happened in San Francisco.
在过去的几天里
and in the last few days,
你会被认为是被抹掉了。
you'll be considered expunged.
当然，你要清楚，
Just so you're clear, of course,
你要是把这事告诉任何人，
you have a breath of word of this to any living soul,
你将度过余生
you will spend the rest of that life.
在最冷，最黑暗的洞里。
in the coldest, darkest hole imaginable.
祝你好运，埃迪。
Good luck, Eddie.
（欢快的音乐）
(upbeat music)
我不会忘记你的，伙计。
I won't forget you, buddy.
（欢快的音乐）
(upbeat music)
回忆唤回回忆唤回你们
Memories bring back memories bring back y'all.
在我们落地前给我最后一支舞
Give me one last dance before we hit the ground.
（欢快的音乐）
(upbeat music)
把我推到超速，这是多么可爱的一种方式
Push me into overdrive what a lovely way to go.
如果你陪在我身边，我就会一路顺风
If you're with me by my side I'm in for the ride.
（欢快的音乐）
(upbeat music)
无处可逃，毒液不等人
There's no running no escape all the venom never waits.
一旦你觉得它刺痛了你的血管，就太晚了
Once you feel it hits your veins it's too late.
你离开以后
You're gone.
（欢快的音乐）
(upbeat music)
没有停，我们在减速
There's no stopping we're slowing down.
在我们落地前给我最后一支舞
Give me one last dance before we hit the ground.
在我们落地之前
Before we hit the ground.
把我推到墙上这是最后的谢幕
Push me up against the wall it's the final curtain call.
要去舞厅了，兄弟，拜托
About to be a ballroom bro oh come on.
（欢快的音乐）
(upbeat music)
没有停，我们在减速
There's no stopping we're slowing down.
现在不会有下次了
There won't be a next time now.
但如果你在我身边我会很好的
But I'll be fine if you're around.
在我们落地前给我最后一支舞
Give me one last dance before we hit the ground.
在我们落地之前
Before we hit the ground.
（欢快的音乐）
(upbeat music)
没有停，我们在减速
There's no stopping we're slowing down.
现在不会有下次了
There won't be a next time now.
但如果你在我身边我会很好的
But I'll be fine if you're around.
在我们落地前给我最后一支舞
Give me one last dance before we hit the ground.
（欢快的音乐）
(upbeat music)
在我们落地之前
Before we hit the ground.
在我们落地之前在我们落地之前
Before we hit the ground Before we hit the ground.
在我们落地之前
Before we hit the ground.
（风）
(wind blowing)
你的冠军倒下了。
Your champion has fallen.
行星将是我的。
The planets will be mine.
黑衣国王醒了。
The king in black is awake.
我会杀了你的世界。
I will kill your world.
每个人都会被烧死。
Everyone will burn.
你会看到的。
And you will watch.